danlok.com 2019-07-04

# Privacy Policy - Dan Lok

This privacy policy lets you know how we collect, use, and protect your personal information. When you visit the website and utilize www.fumoney.com / www.closersinblack.com / www.danlok.com / www.fumoneywithstefan.com / www.fumoneywithjc.com / www.realmenrealcloser.com / www.besthighendcareer.com / www.fumoneywarrior.com / www.fumoneywithmatt.com / www.fumoneywithvince.com / www.fumoneywithchin.com / www.highticketsales.com / www. highticketsalesteam.com / www. fumoneypill.com/ www.fumoneybook.com / www.highendleadgen.com / www.highticketsaleswithjay.com / www.fumoneywithmatt.com / www.milliondollarwebinar.com / www.instantbestsellingauthor.com / domain(s) and all sub domain(s) you accept and agree to the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy. In particular, you consent to the collection and use of your personal information as described in this policy.

We are committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.

We may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from May 2018.

 **What we collect**

We may collect the following information:

name and job title  
contact information including email address  
demographic information such as postcode, preferences and interests  
other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers

 **What we do with the information we gather**

We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:

Internal record keeping.  
We may use the information to improve our products and services.  
We may periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided.  
From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes. We may contact you by email, phone, fax or mail. We may use the information to customize the website according to your interests.

 **Security**

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

 **General Data Privacy Regulation (GDPR)**

The GDPR takes effect on May 25, 2018, and is intended to protect the data of European Union citizens.

As a company that markets its site content, products and/or services online we do not specifically target our marketing to the EU or conduct business in or to the EU in any meaningful way. If the data that you provide to us in the course of your use of our site or services or products is governed by GDPR, we will abide by the relevant portions of the regulation. If you are a resident of the European Economic Area (EEA), or are accessing this site from within the EEA, you may have the right to request: access to, correction of, deletion of; portability of; and restriction or objection to processing, of your personal data, from us. This includes the “right to be forgotten.”

To make any of these requests, please contact our GDPR contact at GDPR@highticketsales.com

 **How we use cookies**

A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer’s hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.

We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.

Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.

You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.

 **Links to other websites**

Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

 **Controlling your personal information**

You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways:

whenever you are asked to fill in a form on the website, look for the box that you can click to indicate that you do not want the information to be used by anybody for direct marketing purposes  
if you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by writing to or emailing us at:

 **dan@highticketsales.com**

We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen.

You may request details of personal information which we hold about you under the Data Protection Act 1998. A small fee will be payable. If you would like a copy of the information held on you please write to:

422 Richards St #170, Vancouver, BC V6B 2Z4 CANADA

If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible, at the above address. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.

Privacy Policy of **www.danlok.com**  
This Website collects some Personal Data from its Users.  
Users may be subject to different protection standards and broader standards may therefore apply to some. In order to learn more about the protection criteria, Users can refer to the applicability section.

 **Policy summary**  
 **Personal Data collected for the following purposes and using the following services:**

Advertising  
Facebook Audience Network  
Personal Data: Cookies, unique device identifiers for advertising (Google Advertiser ID or IDFA, for example) and Usage Data  
Google AdSense  
Personal Data: Cookies and Usage Data  
Analytics  
Facebook Ads conversion tracking, Google Analytics, Google Ads conversion tracking, Hotjar Form Analysis & Conversion Funnels, LinkedIn conversion tracking and Quantcast Measure  
Personal Data: Cookies and Usage Data  
Facebook Analytics for Apps  
Personal Data: Usage Data and various types of Data as specified in the privacy policy of the service  
User ID extension for Google Analytics  
Personal Data: Cookies  
Content commenting  
Facebook Comments  
Personal Data: Cookies and Usage Data  
Displaying content from external platforms  
Google Fonts  
Personal Data: Usage Data and various types of Data as specified in the privacy policy of the service  
Instagram widget and YouTube video widget  
Personal Data: Cookies and Usage Data  
YouTube video widget without cookies  
Personal Data: Usage Data  
Handling payments  
PayPal and Stripe  
Personal Data: various types of Data as specified in the privacy policy of the service  
PayPal Carrier Payments  
Personal Data: phone number and various types of Data as specified in the privacy policy of the service  
Heat mapping and session recording  
Hotjar Heat Maps & Recordings  
Personal Data: Cookies, Usage Data and various types of Data as specified in the privacy policy of the service  
Interaction with data collection platforms and other third parties  
Hotjar Recruit User Testers  
Personal Data: Cookies, Usage Data and various types of Data  
Wufoo widget  
Personal Data: Cookies and Usage Data  
Interaction with external social networks and platforms  
PayPal button and widgets  
Personal Data: Cookies and Usage Data  
Interaction with live chat platforms  
Zendesk Chat  
Personal Data: email address, first name, last name and phone number  
Interaction with support and feedback platforms  
Zendesk Widget  
Personal Data: Cookies, email address, first name and last name  
Managing support and contact requests  
Zendesk  
Personal Data: various types of Data as specified in the privacy policy of the service  
Remarketing and behavioral targeting  
Facebook Custom Audience  
Personal Data: Cookies and email address  
Facebook Remarketing and AdWords Remarketing  
Personal Data: Cookies and Usage Data  
Tag Management  
Google Tag Manager  
Personal Data: Cookies and Usage Data  
Traffic optimization and distribution  
Cloudflare  
Personal Data: Cookies and various types of Data as specified in the privacy policy of the service  
User database management  
ActiveCampaign  
Personal Data: Cookies, email address and various types of Data as specified in the privacy policy of the service  
Contact information

Owner and Data Controller  
Dan Lok, 422 Richards St #170, Vancouver, BC V6B 2Z4 

Owner contact email: support@highticketsales.com

 **Full policy**

 **Owner and Data Controller**  
Dan Lok, 422 Richards St #170 Vancouver BC V6B 2Z4  
Owner contact email: support@highticketsales.com

 **Types of Data collected**  
Among the types of Personal Data that this Website collects, by itself or through third parties, there are: Cookies, Usage Data, unique device identifiers for advertising (Google Advertiser ID or IDFA, for example), email address, various types of Data, phone number, first name and last name.

Complete details on each type of Personal Data collected are provided in the dedicated sections of this privacy policy or by specific explanation texts displayed prior to the Data collection.  
Personal Data may be freely provided by the User, or, in case of Usage Data, collected automatically when using this Website.

Unless specified otherwise, all Data requested by this Website is mandatory and failure to provide this Data may make it impossible for this Website to provide its services. In cases where this Website specifically states that some Data is not mandatory, Users are free not to communicate this Data without consequences to the availability or the functioning of the Service.

Users who are uncertain about which Personal Data is mandatory are welcome to contact the Owner.  
Any use of Cookies – or of other tracking tools – by this Website or by the owners of third-party services used by this Website serves the purpose of providing the Service required by the User, in addition to any other purposes described in the present document and in the Cookie Policy, if available.

Users are responsible for any third-party Personal Data obtained, published or shared through this Website and confirm that they have the third party’s consent to provide the Data to the Owner.

 **Mode and place of processing the Data**  
 **Methods of processing**  
The Owner takes appropriate security measures to prevent unauthorized access, disclosure, modification, or unauthorized destruction of the Data.

The Data processing is carried out using computers and/or IT enabled tools, following organizational procedures and modes strictly related to the purposes indicated. In addition to the Owner, in some cases, the Data may be accessible to certain types of persons in charge, involved with the operation of this Website (administration, sales, marketing, legal, system administration) or external parties (such as third-party technical service providers, mail carriers, hosting providers, IT companies, communications agencies) appointed, if necessary, as Data Processors by the Owner. The updated list of these parties may be requested from the Owner at any time.

 **Legal basis of processing**  
The Owner may process Personal Data relating to Users if one of the following applies:

  * Users have given their consent for one or more specific purposes. Note: Under some legislations the Owner may be allowed to process Personal Data until the User objects to such processing (“opt-out”), without having to rely on consent or any other of the following legal bases. This, however, does not apply, whenever the processing of Personal Data is subject to European data protection law;
  * provision of Data is necessary for the performance of an agreement with the User and/or for any pre-contractual obligations thereof;
  * processing is necessary for compliance with a legal obligation to which the Owner is subject;
  * processing is related to a task that is carried out in the public interest or in the exercise of official authority vested in the Owner;
  * processing is necessary for the purposes of the legitimate interests pursued by the Owner or by a third party.

In any case, the Owner will gladly help to clarify the specific legal basis that applies to the processing, and in particular whether the provision of Personal Data is a statutory or contractual requirement, or a requirement necessary to enter into a contract.

 **Place**  
The Data is processed at the Owner’s operating offices and in any other places where the parties involved in the processing are located.

Depending on the User’s location, data transfers may involve transferring the User’s Data to a country other than their own. To find out more about the place of processing of such transferred Data, Users can check the section containing details about the processing of Personal Data.

If broader protection standards are applicable, Users are also entitled to learn about the legal basis of Data transfers to a country outside the European Union or to any international organization governed by public international law or set up by two or more countries, such as the UN, and about the security measures taken by the Owner to safeguard their Data.

If any such transfer takes place, Users can find out more by checking the relevant sections of this document or inquire with the Owner using the information provided in the contact section.

 **Retention time**  
Personal Data shall be processed and stored for as long as required by the purpose they have been collected for.  
Therefore:

  * Personal Data collected for purposes related to the performance of a contract between the Owner and the User shall be retained until such contract has been fully performed.
  * Personal Data collected for the purposes of the Owner’s legitimate interests shall be retained as long as needed to fulfill such purposes. Users may find specific information regarding the legitimate interests pursued by the Owner within the relevant sections of this document or by contacting the Owner.

The Owner may be allowed to retain Personal Data for a longer period whenever the User has given consent to such processing, as long as such consent is not withdrawn. Furthermore, the Owner may be obliged to retain Personal Data for a longer period whenever required to do so for the performance of a legal obligation or upon order of an authority.

Once the retention period expires, Personal Data shall be deleted. Therefore, the right to access, the right to erasure, the right to rectification and the right to data portability cannot be enforced after expiration of the retention period.

 **The purposes of processing**  
The Data concerning the User is collected to allow the Owner to provide its Services, as well as for the following purposes: Analytics, Advertising, Remarketing and behavioral targeting, Content commenting, User database management, Traffic optimization and distribution, Displaying content from external platforms, Tag Management, Heat mapping and session recording, Interaction with data collection platforms and other third parties, Handling payments, Interaction with external social networks and platforms, Managing support and contact requests, Interaction with live chat platforms and Interaction with support and feedback platforms.

Users can find further detailed information about such purposes of processing and about the specific Personal Data used for each purpose in the respective sections of this document.

 **Detailed information on the processing of Personal Data**  
Personal Data is collected for the following purposes and using the following services:

  *  **Advertising**  
This type of service allows User Data to be utilized for advertising communication purposes displayed in the form of banners and other advertisements on this Website, possibly based on User interests.This does not mean that all Personal Data are used for this purpose. Information and conditions of use are shown below.Some of the services listed below may use Cookies to identify Users or they may use the behavioral retargeting technique, i.e. displaying ads tailored to the User’s interests and behavior, including those detected outside this Website. For more information, please check the privacy policies of the relevant services.In addition to any opt out offered by any of the services below, the User may opt out of a third-party service’s use of cookies by visiting the [Network Advertising Initiative opt-out page](http://optout.networkadvertising.org/). **  
Facebook Audience Network (Facebook, Inc.)**  
Facebook Audience Network is an advertising service provided by Facebook, Inc. **In order to understand Facebook’s use of Data, consult** [Facebook’s data policy](https://www.facebook.com/about/privacy/).

This Website may use identifiers for mobile devices (including Android Advertising ID or Advertising Identifier for iOS, respectively) and technologies similar to cookies to run the Facebook Audience Network service. One of the ways Audience Network shows ads is by using the User’s ad preferences. The User can control this in the [Facebook ad settings](https://www.facebook.com/ads/settings).

Users may opt-out of certain Audience Network targeting through applicable device settings, such as the device advertising settings for mobile phones or by following the instructions in other Audience Network related sections of this privacy policy, if available.

Personal Data collected: Cookies, unique device identifiers for advertising (Google Advertiser ID or IDFA, for example) and Usage Data.  
Place of processing: United States – [Privacy Policy](https://www.facebook.com/about/privacy/) – [Opt Out](https://www.facebook.com/settings?tab=ads). Privacy Shield participant.

 **Google AdSense (Google Inc.)**  
Google AdSense is an advertising service provided by Google Inc. This service uses the “Doubleclick” Cookie, which tracks use of this Website and User behavior concerning ads, products and services offered.

Users may decide to disable all the Doubleclick Cookies by clicking on: [google.com/settings/ads/onweb/optout](https://www.google.com/settings/ads/onweb/optout).

Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage Data.  
Place of processing: United States – [Privacy Policy](https://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/) – [Opt Out](https://www.google.com/settings/ads/onweb/optout). Privacy Shield participant.

  *  **Analytics**  
The services contained in this section enable the Owner to monitor and analyze web traffic and can be used to keep track of User behavior. **Facebook Ads conversion tracking (Facebook, Inc.)**  
Facebook Ads conversion tracking is an analytics service provided by Facebook, Inc. that connects data from the Facebook advertising network with actions performed on this Website.

Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage Data.  
Place of processing: United States – [Privacy Policy](https://www.facebook.com/about/privacy/). Privacy Shield participant.

 **Google Analytics (Google Inc.)**  
Google Analytics is a web analysis service provided by Google Inc. (“Google”). Google utilizes the Data collected to track and examine the use of this Website, to prepare reports on its activities and share them with other Google services.

Google may use the Data collected to contextualize and personalize the ads of its own advertising network.

Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage Data.  
Place of processing: United States – [Privacy Policy](https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/) – [Opt Out](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en). Privacy Shield participant.

 **Facebook Analytics for Apps (Facebook, Inc.)**  
Facebook Analytics for Apps is an analytics service provided by Facebook, Inc.

Personal Data collected: Usage Data and various types of Data as specified in the privacy policy of the service.  
Place of processing: United States – [Privacy Policy](https://www.facebook.com/about/privacy/). Privacy Shield participant.

 **Google Ads conversion tracking (Google Inc.)**  
Google Ads conversion tracking is an analytics service provided by Google Inc. that connects data from the Google Ads advertising network with actions performed on this Website.

Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage Data.  
Place of processing: United States – [Privacy Policy](https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/). Privacy Shield participant.

 **Hotjar Form Analysis & Conversion Funnels (Hotjar Ltd.)**  
Hotjar is an analytics service provided by Hotjar Ltd.  
Hotjar honors generic Do Not Track headers. This means your browser can tell its script not to collect any of your data. This is a setting that is available in all major browsers. Find [Hotjar’s opt-out information here](https://www.hotjar.com/opt-out).

Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage Data.  
Place of processing: Malta – [Privacy Policy](https://www.hotjar.com/privacy) – [Opt Out](https://www.hotjar.com/opt-out).

 **LinkedIn conversion tracking (LinkedIn Corporation)**  
LinkedIn conversion tracking is an analytics service provided by LinkedIn Corporation that connects data from the LinkedIn advertising network with actions performed on this Website.

Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage Data.  
Place of processing: United States – [Privacy Policy](https://www.linkedin.com/legal/privacy-policy).

 **User ID extension for Google Analytics (Google Inc.)**  
Google Analytics on this Website makes use of a feature called User ID. This setup allows for a more accurate tracking of Users by associating that User with the same ID over various sessions and devices. It is set up in a way that doesn’t allow Google to personally identify an individual or permanently identify a particular device.

The User ID extension might make it possible to connect Data from Google Analytics with other Data about the User collected by this Website.

The opt-out link below will only opt you out for the device you are on, but not from tracking performed independently by the Owner. Contact the Owner via the email address provided in this privacy policy to object to the aforementioned tracking as well.

Personal Data collected: Cookies.  
Place of processing: United States – [Privacy Policy](https://www.google.com/intl/policies/privacy/) – [Opt Out](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout). Privacy Shield participant.

 **Quantcast Measure (Quantcast Corporation)**  
Quantcast Measure is an analytics service provided by Quantcast Corporation.

Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage Data.  
Place of processing: United States – [Privacy Policy](https://www.quantcast.com/privacy) – [Opt Out](https://www.quantcast.com/opt-out).

  *  **Content commenting**  
Content commenting services allow Users to make and publish their comments on the contents of this Website.Depending on the settings chosen by the Owner, Users may also leave anonymous comments. If there is an email address among the Personal Data provided by the User, it may be used to send notifications of comments on the same content. Users are responsible for the content of their own comments.If a content commenting service provided by third parties is installed, it may still collect web traffic data for the pages where the comment service is installed, even when Users do not use the content commenting service. **Facebook Comments (Facebook, Inc.)  
** Facebook Comments is a content commenting service provided by Facebook, Inc. enabling the User to leave comments and share them on the Facebook platform.

Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage Data.  
Place of processing: United States – [Privacy Policy](https://www.facebook.com/privacy/explanation). Privacy Shield participant.

  *  **Displaying content from external platforms**  
This type of service allows you to view content hosted on external platforms directly from the pages of this Website and interact with them.This type of service might still collect web traffic data for the pages where the service is installed, even when Users do not use it. **Google Fonts (Google Inc.)**  
Google Fonts is a typeface visualization service provided by Google Inc. that allows this Website to incorporate content of this kind on its pages.

Personal Data collected: Usage Data and various types of Data as specified in the privacy policy of the service.  
Place of processing: United States – [Privacy Policy](https://www.google.it/intl/policies/privacy/). Privacy Shield participant.

Instagram widget (Instagram, Inc.)  
Instagram is an image visualization service provided by Instagram, Inc. that allows this Website to incorporate content of this kind on its pages.

Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage Data.  
Place of processing: United States – [Privacy Policy](https://www.instagram.com/about/legal/privacy/).

 **YouTube video widget (Google Inc.)**  
YouTube is a video content visualization service provided by Google Inc. that allows this Website to incorporate content of this kind on its pages.

Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage Data.  
Place of processing: United States – [Privacy Policy](http://www.google.it/intl/en/policies/privacy/). Privacy Shield participant.

 **YouTube video widget without cookies (Google Inc.)**  
YouTube is a video content visualization service provided by Google Inc. that allows this Website to incorporate content of this kind on its pages.

This widget is set up in a way that ensures that YouTube won’t store information and cookies about Users on this Website unless they play the video.

Personal Data collected: Usage Data.  
Place of processing: United States – [Privacy Policy](http://www.google.it/intl/en/policies/privacy/). Privacy Shield participant.

  *  **Handling payments**  
Payment processing services enable this Website to process payments by credit card, bank transfer or other means. To ensure greater security, this Website shares only the information necessary to execute the transaction with the financial intermediaries handling the transaction.Some of these services may also enable the sending of timed messages to the User, such as emails containing invoices or notifications concerning the payment. **  
PayPal (PayPal Inc.)**  
PayPal is a payment service provided by PayPal Inc., which allows Users to make online payments.  
Personal Data collected: various types of Data as specified in the privacy policy of the service.  
Place of processing: See the PayPal privacy policy – [Privacy Policy](https://www.paypal.com/privacy).

 **PayPal Carrier Payments (PayPal Inc.)**  
PayPal Carrier Payments is a payment service provided by PayPal, Inc., which allows Users to make online payments using their mobile phone operator.

Personal Data collected: phone number and various types of Data as specified in the privacy policy of the service.  
Place of processing: See the PayPal privacy policy – [Privacy Policy](https://www.paypal.com/cgi-bin/webscr?cmd=p/gen/ua/policy_privacy-outside).

 **Stripe (Stripe Inc)**  
Stripe is a payment service provided by Stripe Inc.

Personal Data collected: various types of Data as specified in the privacy policy of the service.  
Place of processing: United States – [Privacy Policy](https://stripe.com/terms/US). Privacy Shield participant.

  *  **Heat mapping and session recording**  
Heat mapping services are used to display the areas of a page where Users most frequently move the mouse or click. This shows where the points of interest are. These services make it possible to monitor and analyze web traffic and keep track of User behavior.Some of these services may record sessions and make them available for later visual playback. **  
Hotjar Heat Maps & Recordings (Hotjar Ltd.)**  
Hotjar is a session recording and heat mapping service provided by Hotjar Ltd.Hotjar honors generic „Do Not Track” headers. This means the browser can tell its script not to collect any of the User’s data. This is a setting that is available in all major browsers. [Find Hotjar’s opt-out information here](https://www.hotjar.com/opt-out).

Personal Data collected: Cookies, Usage Data and various types of Data as specified in the privacy policy of the service.  
Place of processing: Malta – [Privacy Policy](https://www.hotjar.com/privacy) – [Opt Out](https://www.hotjar.com/opt-out).

  *  **Interaction with data collection platforms and other third parties**  
This type of service allows Users to interact with data collection platforms or other services directly from the pages of this Website for the purpose of saving and reusing data.If one of these services is installed, it may collect browsing and Usage Data in the pages where it is installed, even if the Users do not actively use the service. **  
Hotjar Recruit User Testers (Hotjar Ltd.)**  
The Hotjar Recruit User Testers widget is a service for interacting with the Hotjar data collection platform provided by Hotjar Ltd.  
Hotjar honors generic „Do Not Track” headers. This means the browser can tell its script not to collect any of the User’s data. This is a setting that is available in all major browsers. [Find Hotjar’s opt-out information here](https://www.hotjar.com/opt-out).

Personal Data collected: Cookies, Usage Data and various types of Data.  
Place of processing: Malta – [Privacy Policy](https://www.hotjar.com/privacy) – [Opt Out](https://www.hotjar.com/opt-out).

 **Wufoo widget (Wufoo Inc.)**  
The Wufoo widget is a service for interacting with the Wufoo data collection platform provided by Wufoo Inc.

Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage Data.  
Place of processing: United States – [Privacy Policy](http://www.wufoo.com/privacy/).

  *  **Interaction with external social networks and platforms**  
This type of service allows interaction with social networks or other external platforms directly from the pages of this Website.The interaction and information obtained through this Website are always subject to the User’s privacy settings for each social network.This type of service might still collect traffic data for the pages where the service is installed, even when Users do not use it.PayPal button and widgets (PayPal Inc.)

The PayPal button and widgets are services allowing interaction with the PayPal platform provided by PayPal Inc.

Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage Data.  
Place of processing: See the PayPal privacy policy – [Privacy Policy](https://www.paypal.com/cgi-bin/webscr?cmd=p/gen/ua/policy_privacy-outside%20).

  *  **Interaction with live chat platforms**  
This type of service allows Users to interact with third-party live chat platforms directly from the pages of this Website, for contacting and being contacted by this Website support service.If one of these services is installed, it may collect browsing and Usage Data in the pages where it is installed, even if the Users do not actively use the service. Moreover, live chat conversations may be logged.Zendesk Chat (Zendesk, Inc.)

Zendesk Chat is a service for interacting with the Zendesk live chat platform provided by Zendesk, Inc.

Personal Data collected: email address, first name, last name and phone number.  
Place of processing: United States – [Privacy Policy](https://www.zendesk.com/company/customers-partners/privacy-policy/). Privacy Shield participant.

  *  **Interaction with support and feedback platforms**  
This type of service allows Users to interact with third-party support and feedback platforms directly from the pages of this Website.If one of these services is installed, it may collect browsing and Usage Data in the pages where it is installed, even if the Users do not actively use the service. **  
Zendesk Widget (Zendesk, Inc.)**  
The Zendesk Widget is a service for interacting with the Zendesk support and feedback platform provided by Zendesk Inc.

Personal Data collected: Cookies, email address, first name and last name.  
Place of processing: United States – [Privacy Policy](https://www.zendesk.com/company/privacy). Privacy Shield participant.

  *  **Managing support and contact requests**  
This type of service allows this Website to manage support and contact requests received via email or by other means, such as the contact form.The Personal Data processed depend on the information provided by the User in the messages and the means used for communication (e.g. email address). **Zendesk (Zendesk, Inc.)**  
Zendesk is a support and contact request management service provided by Zendesk Inc.  
Personal Data collected: various types of Data as specified in the privacy policy of the service.  
Place of processing: United States – [Privacy Policy](https://www.zendesk.com/company/privacy). Privacy Shield participant.
  *  **Remarketing and behavioral targeting**  
This type of service allows this Website and its partners to inform, optimize and serve advertising based on past use of this Website by the User.This activity is performed by tracking Usage Data and by using Cookies, information that is transferred to the partners that manage the remarketing and behavioral targeting activity.In addition to any opt out offered by any of the services below, the User may opt out of a third-party service’s use of cookies by visiting the [Network Advertising Initiative opt-out page](http://optout.networkadvertising.org/).Facebook Custom Audience (Facebook, Inc.)

Facebook Custom Audience is a remarketing and behavioral targeting service provided by Facebook, Inc. that connects the activity of this Website with the Facebook advertising network.

Personal Data collected: Cookies and email address.  
Place of processing: United States – [Privacy Policy](https://www.facebook.com/about/privacy/) – [Opt Out](https://www.aboutads.info/choices/). Privacy Shield participant.

 **Facebook Remarketing (Facebook, Inc.)**  
Facebook Remarketing is a remarketing and behavioral targeting service provided by Facebook, Inc. that connects the activity of this Website with the Facebook advertising network.

Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage Data.  
Place of processing: United States – [Privacy Policy](https://www.facebook.com/about/privacy/) – [Opt Out](https://www.aboutads.info/choices/). Privacy Shield participant.

 **AdWords Remarketing (Google Inc.)**  
AdWords Remarketing is a remarketing and behavioral targeting service provided by Google Inc. that connects the activity of this Website with the Adwords advertising network and the Doubleclick Cookie.

Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage Data.  
Place of processing: United States – [Privacy Policy](http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/) – [Opt Out](https://www.google.com/settings/ads/onweb/optout).

  *  **Tag Management**  
This type of service helps the Owner to manage the tags or scripts needed on this Website in a centralized fashion.This results in the Users’ Data flowing through these services, potentially resulting in the retention of this Data.Google Tag Manager (Google LLC)

Google Tag Manager is a tag management service provided by Google LLC.

Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage Data.  
Place of processing: United States – [Privacy Policy](https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/). Privacy Shield participant.

  *  **Traffic optimization and distribution**  
This type of service allows this Website to distribute their content using servers located across different countries and to optimize their performance.Which Personal Data are processed depends on the characteristics and the way these services are implemented. Their function is to filter communications between this Website and the User’s browser.Considering the widespread distribution of this system, it is difficult to determine the locations to which the contents that may contain Personal Information User are transferred.Cloudflare (Cloudflare)

Cloudflare is a traffic optimization and distribution service provided by Cloudflare Inc.

The way Cloudflare is integrated means that it filters all the traffic through this Website, i.e., communication between this Website and the User’s browser, while also allowing analytical data from this Website to be collected.

Personal Data collected: Cookies and various types of Data as specified in the privacy policy of the service.  
Place of processing: United States – [Privacy Policy](https://www.cloudflare.com/security-policy/).

  *  **User database management**  
This type of service allows the Owner to build user profiles by starting from an email address, a personal name, or other information that the User provides to this Website, as well as to track User activities through analytics features. This Personal Data may also be matched with publicly available information about the User (such as social networks’ profiles) and used to build private profiles that the Owner can display and use for improving this Website.Some of these services may also enable the sending of timed messages to the User, such as emails based on specific actions performed on this Website. **ActiveCampaign (ActiveCampaign, Inc.)**  
ActiveCampaign is a User database management service provided by ActiveCampaign, Inc.  
Personal Data collected: Cookies, email address and various types of Data as specified in the privacy policy of the service.  
Place of processing: United States – [Privacy Policy](https://www.activecampaign.com/help/privacy-policy/).

 **The rights of Users**  
Users may exercise certain rights regarding their Data processed by the Owner.

Users entitled to broader protection standards may exercise any of the rights described below. In all other cases, Users may inquire with the Owner to find out which rights apply to them.

In particular, Users have the right to do the following:

  *  **Withdraw their consent at any time**. Users have the right to withdraw consent where they have previously given their consent to the processing of their Personal Data.
  *  **Object to processing of their Data**. Users have the right to object to the processing of their Data if the processing is carried out on a legal basis other than consent. Further details are provided in the dedicated section below.
  *  **Access their Data**. Users have the right to learn if Data is being processed by the Owner, obtain disclosure regarding certain aspects of the processing and obtain a copy of the Data undergoing processing.
  *  **Verify and seek rectification**. Users have the right to verify the accuracy of their Data and ask for it to be updated or corrected.
  *  **Restrict the processing of their Data**. Users have the right, under certain circumstances, to restrict the processing of their Data. In this case, the Owner will not process their Data for any purpose other than storing it.
  *  **Have their Personal Data deleted or otherwise removed**. Users have the right, under certain circumstances, to obtain the erasure of their Data from the Owner.
  *  **Receive their Data and have it transferred to another controller**. Users have the right to receive their Data in a structured, commonly used and machine readable format and, if technically feasible, to have it transmitted to another controller without any hindrance. This provision is applicable provided that the Data is processed by automated means and that the processing is based on the User’s consent, on a contract which the User is part of or on pre-contractual obligations thereof.
  *  **Lodge a complaint**. Users have the right to bring a claim before their competent data protection authority.

 **Details about the right to object to processing**  
Where Personal Data is processed for a public interest, in the exercise of an official authority vested in the Owner or for the purposes of the legitimate interests pursued by the Owner, Users may object to such processing by providing a ground related to their particular situation to justify the objection.  
Users must know that, however, should their Personal Data be processed for direct marketing purposes, they can object to that processing at any time without providing any justification. To learn, whether the Owner is processing Personal Data for direct marketing purposes, Users may refer to the relevant sections of this document.  
 **  
How to exercise these rights**  
Any requests to exercise User rights can be directed to the Owner through the contact details provided in this document. These requests can be exercised free of charge and will be addressed by the Owner as early as possible and always within one month.  
 **  
Applicability of broader protection standards**  
While most provisions of this document concern all Users, some provisions expressly only apply if the processing of Personal Data is subject to broader protection standards.

Such broader protection standards apply when the processing:

  * is performed by an Owner based within the EU;
  * concerns the Personal Data of Users who are in the EU and is related to the offering of paid or unpaid goods or services, to such Users;
  * concerns the Personal Data of Users who are in the EU and allows the Owner to monitor such Users’ behavior taking place in the EU.

 **Cookie Policy**  
This Website uses Cookies. To learn more and for a detailed cookie notice, the User may consult the [Cookie Policy](http://www.iubenda.com/privacy-policy/23598845/cookie-policy).  
 **  
Additional information about Data collection and processing**

 **Legal action**  
The User’s Personal Data may be used for legal purposes by the Owner in Court or in the stages leading to possible legal action arising from improper use of this Website or the related Services.  
The User declares to be aware that the Owner may be required to reveal personal data upon request of public authorities.

 **Additional information about User’s Personal Data**  
In addition to the information contained in this privacy policy, this Website may provide the User with additional and contextual information concerning particular Services or the collection and processing of Personal Data upon request.

 **System logs and maintenance**  
For operation and maintenance purposes, this Website and any third-party services may collect files that record interaction with this Website (System logs) use other Personal Data (such as the IP Address) for this purpose.

 **Information not contained in this policy**  
More details concerning the collection or processing of Personal Data may be requested from the Owner at any time. Please see the contact information at the beginning of this document.

 **How “Do Not Track” requests are handled**  
This Website does not support “Do Not Track” requests.  
To determine whether any of the third-party services it uses honor the “Do Not Track” requests, please read their privacy policies.

 **Changes to this privacy policy**  
The Owner reserves the right to make changes to this privacy policy at any time by giving notice to its Users on this page and possibly within this Website and/or – as far as technically and legally feasible – sending a notice to Users via any contact information available to the Owner. It is strongly recommended to check this page often, referring to the date of the last modification listed at the bottom.

Should the changes affect processing activities performed on the basis of the User’s consent, the Owner shall collect new consent from the User, where required.

 **Definitions and legal references  
**  
 **Personal Data (or Data)**  
Any information that directly, indirectly, or in connection with other information — including a personal identification number — allows for the identification or identifiability of a natural person.

 **Usage Data**  
Information collected automatically through this Website (or third-party services employed in this Website), which can include: the IP addresses or domain names of the computers utilized by the Users who use this Website, the URI addresses (Uniform Resource Identifier), the time of the request, the method utilized to submit the request to the server, the size of the file received in response, the numerical code indicating the status of the server’s answer (successful outcome, error, etc.), the country of origin, the features of the browser and the operating system utilized by the User, the various time details per visit (e.g., the time spent on each page within the Application) and the details about the path followed within the Application with special reference to the sequence of pages visited, and other parameters about the device operating system and/or the User’s IT environment.

 **User**  
The individual using this Website who, unless otherwise specified, coincides with the Data Subject.

 **Data Subject**  
The natural person to whom the Personal Data refers.

 **Data Processor (or Data Supervisor)**  
The natural or legal person, public authority, agency or other body which processes Personal Data on behalf of the Controller, as described in this privacy policy.

 **Data Controller (or Owner)**  
The natural or legal person, public authority, agency or other body which, alone or jointly with others, determines the purposes and means of the processing of Personal Data, including the security measures concerning the operation and use of this Website. The Data Controller, unless otherwise specified, is the Owner of this Website.

 **This Website (or this Application)**  
The means by which the Personal Data of the User is collected and processed.

 **Service**  
The service provided by this Website as described in the relative terms (if available) and on this site/application.

 **European Union (or EU)**  
Unless otherwise specified, all references made within this document to the European Union include all current member states to the European Union and the European Economic Area.

 **Cookies**  
Small sets of data stored in the User’s device.

 **Legal information**  
This privacy statement has been prepared based on provisions of multiple legislations, including Art. 13/14 of Regulation (EU) 2016/679 (General Data Protection Regulation).  
This privacy policy relates solely to this Website, if not stated otherwise within this document.  
Latest update: June 06, 2018  
iubenda hosts this content and only collects the Personal Data strictly necessary for it to be provided

 **Cookie Policy of www.danlok.com**  
Cookies consist of portions of code installed in the browser that assist the Owner in providing the Service according to the purposes described. Some of the purposes for which Cookies are installed may also require the User’s consent.

Where the installation of Cookies is based on consent, such consent can be freely withdrawn at any time following the instructions provided in this document.

 **Technical Cookies and Cookies serving aggregated statistical purposes  
**  
 **Activity strictly necessary for the functioning of the Service**  
This Website uses Cookies to save the User’s session and to carry out other activities that are strictly necessary for the operation of this Website, for example in relation to the distribution of traffic.

 **Activity regarding the saving of preferences, optimization, and statistics**  
This Website uses Cookies to save browsing preferences and to optimize the User’s browsing experience. Among these Cookies are, for example, those used for the setting of language and currency preferences or for the management of first party statistics employed directly by the Owner of the site.  
 **Other types of Cookies or third parties that install Cookies**  
Some of the services listed below collect statistics in an anonymized and aggregated form and may not require the consent of the User or may be managed directly by the Owner – depending on how they are described – without the help of third parties.  
If any third party operated services are listed among the tools below, these may be used to track Users’ browsing habits – in addition to the information specified herein and without the Owner’s knowledge. Please refer to the privacy policy of the listed services for detailed information.

 **Advertising**  
This type of service allows User Data to be utilized for advertising communication purposes displayed in the form of banners and other advertisements on this Website, possibly based on User interests.  
This does not mean that all Personal Data are used for this purpose. Information and conditions of use are shown below.

Some of the services listed below may use Cookies to identify Users or they may use the behavioral retargeting technique, i.e. displaying ads tailored to the User’s interests and behavior, including those detected outside this Website. For more information, please check the privacy policies of the relevant services.

In addition to any opt out offered by any of the services below, the User may opt out of a third-party service’s use of cookies by visiting the [Network Advertising Initiative opt-out page](http://optout.networkadvertising.org/).

 **Facebook Audience Network (Facebook, Inc.)**  
Facebook Audience Network is an advertising service provided by Facebook, Inc. **In order to understand Facebook’s use of Data, consult** [Facebook’s data policy](https://www.facebook.com/about/privacy/).

This Website may use identifiers for mobile devices (including Android Advertising ID or Advertising Identifier for iOS, respectively) and technologies similar to cookies to run the Facebook Audience Network service. One of the ways Audience Network shows ads is by using the User’s ad preferences. The User can control this in the [Facebook ad settings](https://www.facebook.com/ads/settings).

Users may opt-out of certain Audience Network targeting through applicable device settings, such as the device advertising settings for mobile phones or by following the instructions in other Audience Network related sections of this privacy policy, if available.

Personal Data collected: Cookies, unique device identifiers for advertising (Google Advertiser ID or IDFA, for example) and Usage Data.  
Place of processing: United States – [Privacy Policy](https://www.facebook.com/about/privacy/) – [Opt Out.](https://www.facebook.com/settings?tab=ads) Privacy Shield participant.

 **Google AdSense (Google Inc.)**  
Google AdSense is an advertising service provided by Google Inc. This service uses the “Doubleclick” Cookie, which tracks use of this Website and User behavior concerning ads, products and services offered.  
Users may decide to disable all the Doubleclick Cookies by clicking on: [google.com/settings/ads/onweb/optout](https://www.google.com/settings/ads/onweb/optout).

Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage Data.  
Place of processing: United States – [Privacy Policy](https://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/) – [Opt Out](https://www.google.com/settings/ads/onweb/optout). Privacy Shield participant.

 **Analytics**  
The services contained in this section enable the Owner to monitor and analyze web traffic and can be used to keep track of User behavior.

 **Facebook Ads conversion tracking (Facebook, Inc.)**  
Facebook Ads conversion tracking is an analytics service provided by Facebook, Inc. that connects data from the Facebook advertising network with actions performed on this Website.

Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage Data.  
Place of processing: United States – [Privacy Policy](https://www.facebook.com/about/privacy/). Privacy Shield participant.

 **Google Analytics (Google Inc.)**  
Google Analytics is a web analysis service provided by Google Inc. (“Google”). Google utilizes the Data collected to track and examine the use of this Website, to prepare reports on its activities and share them with other Google services.

Google may use the Data collected to contextualize and personalize the ads of its own advertising network.

Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage Data.  
Place of processing: United States – [Privacy Policy](https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/) – [Opt Out](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en). Privacy Shield participant.

 **Google Ads conversion tracking (Google Inc.)**  
Google Ads conversion tracking is an analytics service provided by Google Inc. that connects data from the Google Ads advertising network with actions performed on this Website.

Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage Data.  
Place of processing: United States – [Privacy Policy](https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/). Privacy Shield participant.

 **Hotjar Form Analysis & Conversion Funnels (Hotjar Ltd.)**  
Hotjar is an analytics service provided by Hotjar Ltd.

Hotjar honors generic Do Not Track headers. This means your browser can tell its script not to collect any of your data. This is a setting that is available in all major browsers. [Find Hotjar’s opt-out information here](https://www.hotjar.com/opt-out).

Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage Data.  
Place of processing: Malta – [Privacy Policy](https://www.hotjar.com/privacy) – [Opt Out](https://www.hotjar.com/opt-out).

 **LinkedIn conversion tracking (LinkedIn Corporation)**  
LinkedIn conversion tracking is an analytics service provided by LinkedIn Corporation that connects data from the LinkedIn advertising network with actions performed on this Website.

Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage Data.  
Place of processing: United States – [Privacy Policy.](https://www.linkedin.com/legal/privacy-policy)

 **User ID extension for Google Analytics (Google Inc.)**  
Google Analytics on this Website makes use of a feature called User ID. This setup allows for a more accurate tracking of Users by associating that User with the same ID over various sessions and devices. It is set up in a way that doesn’t allow Google to personally identify an individual or permanently identify a particular device.  
The User ID extension might make it possible to connect Data from Google Analytics with other Data about the User collected by this Website.

The opt-out link below will only opt you out for the device you are on, but not from tracking performed independently by the Owner. Contact the Owner via the email address provided in this privacy policy to object to the aforementioned tracking as well.

Personal Data collected: Cookies.  
Place of processing: United States – [Privacy Policy](https://www.google.com/intl/policies/privacy/) – [Opt Out](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout). Privacy Shield participant.

 **Quantcast Measure (Quantcast Corporation)**  
Quantcast Measure is an analytics service provided by Quantcast Corporation.

Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage Data.  
Place of processing: United States – [Privacy Policy](https://www.quantcast.com/privacy) – [Opt Out](https://www.quantcast.com/opt-out).

 **Content commenting**  
Content commenting services allow Users to make and publish their comments on the contents of this Website.

Depending on the settings chosen by the Owner, Users may also leave anonymous comments. If there is an email address among the Personal Data provided by the User, it may be used to send notifications of comments on the same content. Users are responsible for the content of their own comments.

If a content commenting service provided by third parties is installed, it may still collect web traffic data for the pages where the comment service is installed, even when Users do not use the content commenting service.

 **Facebook Comments (Facebook, Inc.)**  
Facebook Comments is a content commenting service provided by Facebook, Inc. enabling the User to leave comments and share them on the Facebook platform.

Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage Data.  
Place of processing: United States – [Privacy Policy](https://www.facebook.com/privacy/explanation). Privacy Shield participant.

 **Displaying content from external platforms**  
This type of service allows you to view content hosted on external platforms directly from the pages of this Website and interact with them.

This type of service might still collect web traffic data for the pages where the service is installed, even when Users do not use it.

 **Instagram widget (Instagram, Inc.)**  
Instagram is an image visualization service provided by Instagram, Inc. that allows this Website to incorporate content of this kind on its pages.

Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage Data.  
Place of processing: United States – [Privacy Policy](https://www.instagram.com/about/legal/privacy/).

 **YouTube video widget (Google Inc.)**  
YouTube is a video content visualization service provided by Google Inc. that allows this Website to incorporate content of this kind on its pages.

Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage Data.  
Place of processing: United States – [Privacy Policy](http://www.google.it/intl/en/policies/privacy/). Privacy Shield participant.

 **Heat mapping and session recording**  
Heat mapping services are used to display the areas of a page where Users most frequently move the mouse or click. This shows where the points of interest are. These services make it possible to monitor and analyze web traffic and keep track of User behavior.

Some of these services may record sessions and make them available for later visual playback.

 **Hotjar Heat Maps & Recordings (Hotjar Ltd.)**  
Hotjar is a session recording and heat mapping service provided by Hotjar Ltd.

Hotjar honors generic „Do Not Track” headers. This means the browser can tell its script not to collect any of the User’s data. This is a setting that is available in all major browsers. Find Hotjar’s opt-out information here.

Personal Data collected: Cookies, Usage Data and various types of Data as specified in the privacy policy of the service.  
Place of processing: Malta – [Privacy Policy](https://www.hotjar.com/privacy) – [Opt Out.](https://www.hotjar.com/opt-out)

 **Interaction with data collection platforms and other third parties**  
This type of service allows Users to interact with data collection platforms or other services directly from the pages of this Website for the purpose of saving and reusing data.

If one of these services is installed, it may collect browsing and Usage Data in the pages where it is installed, even if the Users do not actively use the service.

 **Hotjar Recruit User Testers (Hotjar Ltd.)**  
The Hotjar Recruit User Testers widget is a service for interacting with the Hotjar data collection platform provided by Hotjar Ltd.

Hotjar honors generic „Do Not Track” headers. This means the browser can tell its script not to collect any of the User’s data. This is a setting that is available in all major browsers. Find Hotjar’s opt-out information here.

Personal Data collected: Cookies, Usage Data and various types of Data.  
Place of processing: Malta – [Privacy Policy](https://www.hotjar.com/privacy) – [Opt Out](https://www.hotjar.com/opt-out).

 **Wufoo widget (Wufoo Inc.)**  
The Wufoo widget is a service for interacting with the Wufoo data collection platform provided by Wufoo Inc.

Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage Data.  
Place of processing: United States – [Privacy Policy](http://www.wufoo.com/privacy/).

 **Interaction with external social networks and platforms**  
This type of service allows interaction with social networks or other external platforms directly from the pages of this Website.

The interaction and information obtained through this Website are always subject to the User’s privacy settings for each social network.  
This type of service might still collect traffic data for the pages where the service is installed, even when Users do not use it.

 **PayPal button and widgets (PayPal Inc.)**  
The PayPal button and widgets are services allowing interaction with the PayPal platform provided by PayPal Inc.

Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage Data.  
Place of processing: See the PayPal privacy policy – [Privacy Policy](https://www.paypal.com/cgi-bin/webscr?cmd=p/gen/ua/policy_privacy-outside%20).

 **Interaction with support and feedback platforms**  
This type of service allows Users to interact with third-party support and feedback platforms directly from the pages of this Website.  
If one of these services is installed, it may collect browsing and Usage Data in the pages where it is installed, even if the Users do not actively use the service.

 **Zendesk Widget (Zendesk, Inc.)**  
The Zendesk Widget is a service for interacting with the Zendesk support and feedback platform provided by Zendesk Inc.

Personal Data collected: Cookies, email address, first name and last name.  
Place of processing: United States – [Privacy Policy](https://www.zendesk.com/company/privacy). Privacy Shield participant.

 **Remarketing and behavioral targeting**  
This type of service allows this Website and its partners to inform, optimize and serve advertising based on past use of this Website by the User.

This activity is performed by tracking Usage Data and by using Cookies, information that is transferred to the partners that manage the remarketing and behavioral targeting activity.

In addition to any opt out offered by any of the services below, the User may opt out of a third-party service’s use of cookies by visiting the [Network Advertising Initiative opt-out page.](http://optout.networkadvertising.org/)

 **Facebook Custom Audience (Facebook, Inc.)**  
Facebook Custom Audience is a remarketing and behavioral targeting service provided by Facebook, Inc. that connects the activity of this Website with the Facebook advertising network.

Personal Data collected: Cookies and email address.  
Place of processing: United States – [Privacy Policy](https://www.facebook.com/about/privacy/) – [Opt Out](https://www.aboutads.info/choices/). Privacy Shield participant.

 **Facebook Remarketing (Facebook, Inc.)**  
Facebook Remarketing is a remarketing and behavioral targeting service provided by Facebook, Inc. that connects the activity of this Website with the Facebook advertising network.

Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage Data.  
Place of processing: United States –[ Privacy Policy](http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/) – [Opt Out](https://www.google.com/settings/ads/onweb/optout). Privacy Shield participant.

 **AdWords Remarketing (Google Inc.)**  
AdWords Remarketing is a remarketing and behavioral targeting service provided by Google Inc. that connects the activity of this Website with the Adwords advertising network and the Doubleclick Cookie.

Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage Data.  
Place of processing: United States – [Privacy Policy](http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/) – [Opt Out](https://www.google.com/settings/ads/onweb/optout).

 **Tag Management**  
This type of service helps the Owner to manage the tags or scripts needed on this Website in a centralized fashion.

This results in the Users’ Data flowing through these services, potentially resulting in the retention of this Data.

 **Google Tag Manager (Google LLC)**  
Google Tag Manager is a tag management service provided by Google LLC.

Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage Data.  
Place of processing: United States – [Privacy Policy.](https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/) Privacy Shield participant.

 **Traffic optimization and distribution**  
This type of service allows this Website to distribute their content using servers located across different countries and to optimize their performance.

Which Personal Data are processed depends on the characteristics and the way these services are implemented. Their function is to filter communications between this Website and the User’s browser.  
Considering the widespread distribution of this system, it is difficult to determine the locations to which the contents that may contain Personal Information User are transferred.

 **Cloudflare (Cloudflare)**  
Cloudflare is a traffic optimization and distribution service provided by Cloudflare Inc.

The way Cloudflare is integrated means that it filters all the traffic through this Website, i.e., communication between this Website and the User’s browser, while also allowing analytical data from this Website to be collected.

Personal Data collected: Cookies and various types of Data as specified in the privacy policy of the service.  
Place of processing: United States – [Privacy Policy](https://www.cloudflare.com/security-policy/).

 **User database management**  
This type of service allows the Owner to build user profiles by starting from an email address, a personal name, or other information that the User provides to this Website, as well as to track User activities through analytics features. This Personal Data may also be matched with publicly available information about the User (such as social networks’ profiles) and used to build private profiles that the Owner can display and use for improving this Website.

Some of these services may also enable the sending of timed messages to the User, such as emails based on specific actions performed on this Website.

 **ActiveCampaign (ActiveCampaign, Inc.)**  
ActiveCampaign is a User database management service provided by ActiveCampaign, Inc.

Personal Data collected: Cookies, email address and various types of Data as specified in the privacy policy of the service.  
Place of processing: United States – [Privacy Policy](https://www.activecampaign.com/help/privacy-policy/).

 **How to provide or withdraw consent to the installation of Cookies**  
In addition to what is specified in this document, the User can manage preferences for Cookies directly from within their own browser and prevent – for example – third parties from installing Cookies.  
Through browser preferences, it is also possible to delete Cookies installed in the past, including the Cookies that may have saved the initial consent for the installation of Cookies by this website.  
Users can, for example, find information about how to manage Cookies in the most commonly used browsers at the following addresses: [Google Chrome](https://support.google.com/chrome/answer/95647?hl=en&p=cpn_cookies), [Mozilla Firefox](https://support.mozilla.org/en-US/kb/enable-and-disable-cookies-website-preferences), [Apple Safari](https://support.apple.com/guide/safari/manage-cookies-and-website-data-sfri11471/) and [Microsoft Internet Explorer](http://windows.microsoft.com/en-us/windows-vista/block-or-allow-cookies).

With regard to Cookies installed by third parties, Users can manage their preferences and withdrawal of their consent by clicking the related opt-out link (if provided), by using the means provided in the third party’s privacy policy, or by contacting the third party.

Notwithstanding the above, the Owner informs that Users may follow the instructions provided on the subsequently linked initiatives by the [EDAA (EU),](http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/) the [Network Advertising Initiative](https://www.networkadvertising.org/understanding-digital-advertising) (US) and the [Digital Advertising Alliance](https://www.aboutads.info/consumers/) (US), [DAAC](https://youradchoices.ca/understanding-online-advertising/) (Canada), [DDAI](http://www.ddai.info/optout) (Japan) or other similar services. Such initiatives allow Users to select their tracking preferences for most of the advertising tools. The Owner thus recommends that Users make use of these resources in addition to the information provided in this document.

 **Owner and Data Controller**  
422 Richards St #170, Vancouver, BC V6B 2Z4   
 **Owner contact email:** support@highticketsales.com

Since the installation of third-party Cookies and other tracking systems through the services used within this Website cannot be technically controlled by the Owner, any specific references to Cookies and tracking systems installed by third parties are to be considered indicative. In order to obtain complete information, the User is kindly requested to consult the privacy policy for the respective third-party services listed in this document.

Given the objective complexity surrounding the identification of technologies based on Cookies, Users are encouraged to contact the Owner should they wish to receive any further information on the use of Cookies by this Website.

 **Definitions and legal references**

 **Personal Data (or Data)**  
Any information that directly, indirectly, or in connection with other information — including a personal identification number — allows for the identification or identifiability of a natural person.

 **Usage Data**  
Information collected automatically through this Website (or third-party services employed in this Website), which can include: the IP addresses or domain names of the computers utilized by the Users who use this Website, the URI addresses (Uniform Resource Identifier), the time of the request, the method utilized to submit the request to the server, the size of the file received in response, the numerical code indicating the status of the server’s answer (successful outcome, error, etc.), the country of origin, the features of the browser and the operating system utilized by the User, the various time details per visit (e.g., the time spent on each page within the Application) and the details about the path followed within the Application with special reference to the sequence of pages visited, and other parameters about the device operating system and/or the User’s IT environment.

 **User**  
The individual using this Website who, unless otherwise specified, coincides with the Data Subject.

 **Data Subject**  
The natural person to whom the Personal Data refers.

 **Data Processor (or Data Supervisor)**  
The natural or legal person, public authority, agency or other body which processes Personal Data on behalf of the Controller, as described in this privacy policy.

 **Data Controller (or Owner)**  
The natural or legal person, public authority, agency or other body which, alone or jointly with others, determines the purposes and means of the processing of Personal Data, including the security measures concerning the operation and use of this Website. The Data Controller, unless otherwise specified, is the Owner of this Website.

 **This Website (or this Application)**  
The means by which the Personal Data of the User is collected and processed.

 **Service**  
The service provided by this Website as described in the relative terms (if available) and on this site/application.

 **European Union (or EU)**  
Unless otherwise specified, all references made within this document to the European Union include all current member states to the European Union and the European Economic Area.

 **Cookies**  
Small sets of data stored in the User’s device.

 **Legal information**  
This privacy statement has been prepared based on provisions of multiple legislations, including Art. 13/14 of Regulation (EU) 2016/679 (General Data Protection Regulation).  
This privacy policy relates solely to this Website, if not stated otherwise within this document.
